<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Alcohol synthesizer -->

  <BM_SpacerAlcoholSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>Alcohol synthesizer module</BM_SpacerAlcoholSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerAlcoholSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into a liver or any compatible artificial liver replacement. This particular model is capable of synthesizing alcohol and releasing it into the body. It's able to suppress alcohol cravings, but properly curing an addiction is not possible with an implant such as this one.</BM_SpacerAlcoholSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>


  <!-- Psychite synthesizer -->

  <BM_SpacerPsychiteSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>Psychite synthesizer module</BM_SpacerPsychiteSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerPsychiteSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into a liver or any compatible artificial liver replacement. This particular model is capable of synthesizing small doses of substances similar in composition to well-known psychite products and releasing them into the body. It’s able to suppress psychite cravings, but properly curing an addiction is not possible with an implant such as this one.</BM_SpacerPsychiteSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>


  <!-- Smokeleaf synthesizer -->

  <BM_SpacerSmokeleafSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>Smokeleaf synthesizer module</BM_SpacerSmokeleafSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerSmokeleafSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into a liver or any compatible artificial liver replacement. This particular model is capable of synthesizing small doses of substances similar in composition to well-known smokeleaf products and releasing them into the body. It's able to suppress smokeleaf cravings, but properly curing an addiction is not possible with an implant such as this one.</BM_SpacerSmokeleafSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>


  <!-- GoJuice synthesizer -->

  <BM_SpacerGoJuiceSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>go-juice synthesizer module</BM_SpacerGoJuiceSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerGoJuiceSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into a liver or any compatible artificial liver replacement. This particular model is capable of synthesizing small doses of go-juice and releasing them into the body. It's able to suppress go-juice cravings, but properly curing an addiction is not possible with an implant such as this one.</BM_SpacerGoJuiceSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>


  <!-- WakeUp synthesizer -->

  <BM_SpacerWakeUpSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>wake-up synthesizer module</BM_SpacerWakeUpSynthesizerUtilityModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerWakeUpSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into a liver or any compatible artificial liver replacement. This particular model is capable of synthesizing small doses of wake-up and releasing them into the body. It’s able to suppress wake-up cravings, but properly curing an addiction is not possible with an implant such as this one.</BM_SpacerWakeUpSynthesizerUtilityModule.description>


</LanguageData>