<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- pyroweave -->

  <BM_SpacerPyroweaveSupportModule.label>pyroweave module</BM_SpacerPyroweaveSupportModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerPyroweaveSupportModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into any compatible artificial limb or spine replacement. This particular model, upon detecting an attack on the user, sends out a directional burst of highly combustible micro-gas toward the attacker through the module's vent-like openings. Due to its limited effective range it is most potent in close-quarters combat, especially against assailants within melee range.</BM_SpacerPyroweaveSupportModule.description>


  <!-- magweave -->

  <BM_SpacerMagweaveSupportModule.label>magweave module</BM_SpacerMagweaveSupportModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerMagweaveSupportModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into any compatible artificial limb or spine replacement. This particular model, upon detecting an attack on the user, sends out a directional electromagnetic pulse towards the attacker. Due to its limited effective range it is most potent in close-quarters combat, especially against assailants within melee range.</BM_SpacerMagweaveSupportModule.description>


  <!-- cryoweave -->

  <BM_SpacerCryoweaveSupportModule.label>cryoweave module</BM_SpacerCryoweaveSupportModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerCryoweaveSupportModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into any compatible artificial limb or spine replacement. This particular model, upon detecting an attack on the user, sends out a directional burst of cryogenic micro-gas toward the attacker through the module's vent-like openings. Due to its limited effective range it is most potent in close-quarters combat, especially against assailants within melee range.</BM_SpacerCryoweaveSupportModule.description>


  <!-- toxweave -->

  <BM_SpacerToxweaveSupportModule.label>toxweave module</BM_SpacerToxweaveSupportModule.label>
  <BM_SpacerToxweaveSupportModule.description>A high-tech device that can be installed into any compatible artificial limb or spine replacement. This particular model, upon detecting an attack on the user, sends out a directional burst of toxic micro-gas toward the attacker through the module's vent-like openings. Due to its limited effective range it is most potent in close-quarters combat, especially against assailants within melee range.</BM_SpacerToxweaveSupportModule.description>


</LanguageData>